[{"answer": "You know, when the vote started getting counted we knew pretty quickly we have -- you know, we have a fairly sophisticated model.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "It's all going to plan?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Were you pleased about the level of the turnout?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "But I think the problem for the Republican Party is that the center of gravity has shifted so far to the right that they're way out of the mainstream.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "If you were putting your strategist's hat on and looking at their campaign, where do you think they really, in the end, lost it?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, I think that he certainly bears some -- people want cooperation on both sides.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "But how much of the responsibility lies with him, with Speaker Boehner, do you think?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I do believe the economy is improving, but I want to challenge a bit of your premise because one of the reasons the economy is improving is because this president was brave.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Are you hoping you're going to get the kind of economic security if not prosperity in this term that will allow you to do perhaps the things Barack Obama, when you sailed in on hope and change, hoped he could do?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "One is, I understand that the first person the president called after knowing that he won was Bill Clinton, is that right?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, there's no question about it.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Does he feel a big debt of gratitude to him?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, I know this has the subject of a lot of discussion.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Are you a relieved man this morning?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Well, it was a very exciting night.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "What was the mood like as victory became a reality?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "He was -- he was, you know, over the moon.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "And how is your father about it?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm going to leave the strategy, obviously, to David Axelrod and to the president and his staff, and his chief of staff, Jack Lew, and my father.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "What is the strategy here?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "His plan is to get to work.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What's your father's plan now?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Well, I think he is.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "He must be feeling pretty proud, isn't he?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Well, he didn't get it done.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "The former CEO of G.E. joins me now to talk about the election, the fallout and -- well, what happened to your mate, Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "You know, I -- he didn't get the minorities, he didn't get the young women.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "But, I mean, look, the Republicans have got to be less intransigent, too, haven't they?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "You know, that's the second guessing, and I don't know.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Would he had been bolder and braver, perhaps most successful had he gone for Marco Rubio or Condoleezza Rice, somebody a bit different from Paul Ryan who looked like a younger version of Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Well, Marco Rubio is a very appealing guy.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "But who's the kinder of person?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "-- changing demographics.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Christie?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "It is Mother Nature's one-two punch.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Tell me what it's like where you are, but also what is your view of the repeated storms we're seeing at the moment?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "A lot of it was just relief.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "When you woke up this morning, what were the things that went through your mind?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Look, at the end of the day, we know what our problems are.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "What do you want to see him really going harder at?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Well, the margin was pretty typically for a successfully elected incumbent.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "What do you put the blame down to for the loss of support amongst women?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Hang on.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Was it number four?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Look, I think it was so clear last night.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Cecile?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Let's agree on one thing.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Where is that in the exit polls?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I was actually on with you, Kelly Anne, on a panel where you said women didn't care about women's health issues.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Can I see that quote please?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Is he capable of delivering the old American dream now in a second term?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I don't know that Paul Ryan hurt him that much, because I think, at the end of the day, people don't vote for the vice president.", "docId": "121107pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Should he have gone for a braver pick, a Marco Rubio, a Condoleezza Rice?", "qSentId": 601}]